<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Tech Tales and Fails</title><link>https://techtales.fail/</link><description>Recent content on Tech Tales and Fails</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 15:51:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://techtales.fail/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Number 1</title><link>https://techtales.fail/01/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 15:51:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://techtales.fail/01/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Join In</title><link>https://techtales.fail/joinin/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 15:51:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://techtales.fail/joinin/</guid><description>&lt;p>There are two ways to join in with the podcast. You can either be a guest or submit an anonymous story.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Remember that this is a light-hearted podcast and we are looking for funny, embarrassing, or just plain silly stories that also have a lesson to teach or to show newcomers that even the experts screw up!&lt;/p>
&lt;h1 id="guest">Guest&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>If you would like to be a guest please fill in the form at this &lt;a href="https://tales.fail/guest">form at this link&lt;/a> and we will get back to you.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Craig</title><link>https://techtales.fail/host/craig/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 15:51:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://techtales.fail/host/craig/</guid><description>&lt;p>Craig brings data and automation together. He loves to learn and share what he learns with the technical community. He enjoys running and lives for his family. He/Him&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Episode 00</title><link>https://techtales.fail/00/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 15:51:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://techtales.fail/00/</guid><description>&lt;p>This is a thing that things do and such&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Rob</title><link>https://techtales.fail/host/rob/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 15:51:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://techtales.fail/host/rob/</guid><description>&lt;p>Rob was a SQL Server DBA with a passion for PowerShell, Azure, Automation, and SQL (PaaS geddit?). Now he just helps people make things. He is a Data Platform MVP and an Azure MVP, a PowerShell Conference Europe organiser, and maintainer of many open-source projects. He has spoken at and volunteered at many Data and PowerShell events all over the world. He is a proud supporter of the Data and PowerShell communities.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>What is Tech Tales and Fails?</title><link>https://techtales.fail/about/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 15:50:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://techtales.fail/about/</guid><description>&lt;p>Each episode, we sit down with folks from the data and tech world to hear about the times things didn’t quite go as planned.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>From accidental table drops to queries that brought down entire systems, we’re diving into the mistakes that made us sweat—but also taught us something valuable along the way.Because let’s be real—everyone messes up. The important thing is what we learn from it.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>So, grab a coffee, take a deep breath, and listen to us talk about tech tales and fails with the most inspiring experts to ever show up on the whole internet.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>John Doe</title><link>https://techtales.fail/guest/firstnamelastname/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://techtales.fail/guest/firstnamelastname/</guid><description>&lt;p>Spoon fresh pie ingredients groceries oranges luncheon farm. Broth chick peas Chinese food indie foods. Cream heating cheese food locally grown first class caramelize restaurant grocery shopping savory chick peas. Recommendations lovely starter soda herbes fridge chocolate eat better quinoa sausage java chef locally grown wholesome. Broil sweet sushi lasagna cream indian. Desert sour vegetarian sous-chef soda oven tasty eat better rice recommendations relish salt butter grape. Grocery shopping delicious Chinese food beets conserve ginger. Authentic blend drink sausage. Groceries sour desert. Take away lasagna consumer luncheon scent cookie beer groceries meals restaurants java cheese vegan chick peas.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>